New Sumiya
I apologize for bothering you
with such an unexpected request.
Thank you so much for taking care of it.
That's all right.
I am sure that the guest who brought
these in will be pleased with your work.
I do hope so. Thank you very much
for entrusting us with them.
Kinme-san, was it? If something else
comes up, we may be contacting you again.
Of course! Kinme Cleaning
would be very happy to serve you.
This is the front desk.
Yes. So you are finished with the bath?
The ceiling is so high!
Yes. I'll be sure to replace those later.
I've never been to such
a magnificent old inn before.
Oh. Yes. I see.
Thank you for letting me know.
It sounds like they
just finished cleaning.
Really? In that case...
I feel this must be another good sign.
If you have time,
would you like to take a dip?
We have an open-air bath on the roof
that we call the Sky-High Bath.
Would you like to try it out?
Wash It
All Away
Ahh.
Episode 6    Pop, Pop, Boom
This really is sky high!
It was time for my lunch break anyway.
I'm sure this is fine.
The festival...
I had so much fun.
Thank you very much.
The water was just right.
My pleasure. I'm glad you enjoyed it.
The view was also amazing.
Truly spectacular!
I do feel a little ashamed using the bath
when I came for a delivery, though.
It's quite all right.
Oh, actually,
since you're already here, would you mind
if I asked you to do one more thing?
This time it's not for a guest.
Of course. I would be happy to help.
Didn't you also say that you could
clean items other than clothes?
Yes, I did.
We also clean bags, shoes, leather
and fabric accessories, and oth—
This is who I meant.
A traditional Japanese doll?
I happened to find her the other day
when I was cleaning at home.
I bought her for my daughter
when she was little,
so it doesn't seem right
to just throw her away.
I thought I might clean her up
so I can put her on display somewhere.
At first, I was planning
to clean her myself,
but as soon as I tried combing her hair,
it got tangled up and I was afraid of
damaging it or yanking some out.
It appears a little too difficult for me.
What do you think? Or is a doll
too far outside your area of expertise?
The fabric looks like
it's probably real kimono material.
Her makeup still remains intact,
but her face and hands are filthy.
But this is probably grime
from being handled.
The hostess's daughter must have
taken this doll with her everywhere.
Um, I've never taken care of
a traditional doll before,
so I'm not sure if it will live up
to your expectations or not,
but I will do my best
to restore her to her original beauty.
Please allow me to give it a try.
New Sumiya
This might turn out to be
a pretty difficult job.
I felt like I owed her
for letting me use the bath for free.
But I shouldn't turn down a request
from a brand new customer, anyway.
Hopefully, this will lead to
other opportunities as well.
Kyusho-kun!
Hello. You're sure out early today.
Yeah. We just had
the end-of-term assembly.
Oh, that's right. Students go on
summer break starting tomorrow.
I'm so jealous!
Well, actually, I get stuck helping out
at home because the inn gets so busy.
We're right on the beach,
so we get tons of tourists,
and there are fireworks shows
like every week.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Yes, that would be a lot to handle.
But since it finally is summer vacation,
be sure to drop it off sometime, okay?
Huh?
I still haven't forgotten about it.
Sure. Another time.
Welcome.
Even if it's my first time,
the essential principles of washing
and stain removal are the same.
Examine the condition closely...
and assess the nature of the stains.
Work without haste...
and with great care.
Wait.
I don't know why, but...
This should be my first time
working on a Japanese doll,
and yet it somehow feels very familiar.
Oh, I see.
I must have done jobs like this
before I lost my memory.
New Sumiya
Oh my goodness!
Just look at how clean she's gotten!
Thank you so much for this.
Not at all.
And right on the heels of your last job.
So how about you take a break
in our grand bath this time?
Oh, no. I can't keep imposing on you.
Please, be my guest.
You do like hot springs, don't you?
Ladies
Atami Hot Springs
Now let's see what tomorrow brings.
Wash It All Away
Atami Moon Terrace
Guesthouse Inn Ishimochi
Sure. Another time.
Oh.
Hmm.
Kinme-san!
Over here.
Oh! Good morning!
You're always such an early bird.
Yes, the town is usually
pretty quiet at this hour.
You can say that again.
Oh, actually, this is great timing.
Can I send some laundry along with you?
Certainly.
I meant to take it to you a few days back,
but things get so busy this time of year.
Well, it is summer vacation.
Tonight is another fireworks show,
so we're all booked up.
Oh, there's another one tonight?
Atami
Seaside Fireworks Show
A Symphony of Fireworks Painting the Sky with Seasonal Colors
Spring
Summer
Fall
Winter
Please help us keep your trip to Atami safe and comfortable.
Yeah. It's pretty much every week now.
So is Kyusho-kun lending a hand again?
Sure is.
I'm running him ragged these days.
He's in the back. Should I get him?
No, that's all right.
Anyway, I'll take care of these.
Thanks a bunch!
Sure.
All right.
Have a good time!
See you later!
Bye-bye!
Buzz, buzz-buzz, bu-bu-bu-buzz.
I guess it's that season again.
Hey there, twins!
Sup!
Heya!
If you're just killing time,
come and give me a hand.
No can do! We're on our way
to work right now, ma'am!
Oh! That looks like a Kyu-kun!
Hey!
Man, it's so hot outside!
Must be nice in there.
Nah, it's really hot inside too.
We don't even have the AC on.
Gotta go.
Okay. Later!
See ya!
Kinme Cleaning
Kyu.
The guests will be arriving soon.
Okay.
Oh, hey, I saw Kinme-san this morning.
You didn't have anything
for her to wash, did you?
No, not right now.
No? Okay, good.
Oh?
It looks like this button is coming loose.
Yeah.
I'll fix this one for you on the house.
I appreciate that.
I'm no good with stuff like that.
Guesthouse Inn Ishimochi
Welcome! Glad to have you!
I can take your luggage.
I'll show you to your room.
This way, please.
Start
Pause
Magisa
Sure is busy.
Yes.
It definitely is summer vacation.
Yeah.
Huh?
What's wrong?
What?
I never see you with such a long face.
Oh.
Well, actually, at the festival
the other day...
Whoa! With a customer's kid?
Shh!
H-Honestly, it was just an accident.
I was still wearing my festival mask,
but our lips did sort of
bump against each other.
Oh, come on. Then it doesn't even count.
B-But ever since then,
I've felt like he's been avoiding me.
Huh.
Th-That must mean
I made him uncomfortable, right?
Huh?
H-How am I ever supposed
to face that customer again?
Huh?
What? Huh?
That is so like you, Kinme-san.
Wh-What do you...
The kid is still in high school, right?
Uh, yes.
You didn't make him uncomfortable.
He's probably just embarrassed about it.
Embarrassed? But why?
The fact that you don't get it
is so adorable, Kinme-san.
Don't waste any energy worrying about it.
It'll work itself out in time.
A-Are you sure about that?
Yeah, I'm sure about that.
Hah! Hilarious.
'Scuse me. I brought you some more water.
Thank... you.
K... Kuriru-chan!
Oh, Kinme-san? Sup.
What are you doing?
How long have you been here?
What am I doing? My job.
And how long? Well, before you
and your friend came in.
Oh, the girl who took your order
is another part-timer.
You two know each other?
Sup. She's my wardrobe advisor.
Oh, I should have guessed.
Kuriru-chan, did you, uh,
hear all of that?
All of what?
Wh-What we were talking about.
Huh? Not a word.
I'm way too busy right now.
Can I order, please?
Ah, coming!
Anyway, enjoy.
I can't be talking about things
like that in public.
I need to be more careful.
Oh, sounds like they're starting.
Yes, it does.
Let's pay up and head outside.
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Whoa!
Wow!
It's so pretty.
Hey, son. Another beer, please.
Sure.
Translation:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michael Arnold
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Riley Dalton
Sriram Gurunathan
Sushi
Here ya go.
Come in. Go ahead and take a seat.
Plates, tea cups,
beer mugs, kanpyo rolls...
It gets way too busy on fireworks days!
Ugh, fireworks.
Episode 7  You Should Leverage Your Assets!!
Next time is "You Should
Leverage Your Assets."